

MARÍA MEDINA

www.mmcprojects.dev

medinamaria90@gmail.com Phone: 603595370

ABOUT ME

I am a software developer with +7 years of experience in the finance sector. Proficient in back-end development and Linux consoles. Currently studying at the renowned 42 programming school. Financial analysis, data analysis with python, modeling, valuation, accounting, and tax controlling in Real Estate and Renewable Energy projects.

SKILLS

- Programming: C, Python, PHP, Javascript, bash, linux.
- Web develoment: Django, Flask, SQL, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, react.
- Automation of work processes
- Financial Skills: Debt management, accounting, taxation, cash flow analysis
- Excel: Financial modelling, macros, building models from scratch.
- Self-learning: Highly focused on expanding skill set
- Communication: Experienced in client interaction, providing solutions

Work Experience

Back-end developer Freelance projects (Dec 2022 - Current)

- Developed and deployed complete web applications using Python (Django & Flask framework), SQL, JavaScript, React and Bootstrap. *Check my projects at my portfolio*.
- Built a web scraping tool for a SEO company to track keyword rankings and automate data collection, saving a lot of time to SEO technicians.
- Colaborated with a renowned author to develop its website (www.currocanete.com). Successfully implemented an online academy within the website. Using Wordpress, PHP, Javascript, HTML and CSS.
- Worked on various projects involving C language, Python, and other technologies.

Financial Analyst with python (Nov 2020 - Dec 2022) Urbania International (Real Estate), Málaga, Spain

- Developed and implemented complex financial models for Residential Development, Build-To-Rent, co-working, PBSA and Equity lending. Data analysis and model automation with Python.
- Monitored investments. Reported to international funds investors through regular communications.
- Assisted in financial Due Diligence for M&A transactions.
- Tresury forecasting for investment decisions and capital calls.
 Utilized Python scripting for data extraction and forecasting calculations

Financial Controller (Feb 2016 - Nov 2020)
Celeo (Energy transmition & Generation), Madrid, SPAIN

- Provided accounting and tax control for the Spanish renewable energy portfolio projects. Administered cash flow forecasting and equity financing.
- Consolidated financial statements and managed auditing processes. Reported financial models, cash flows and debt covenant to fund bondholders.

Accounting & Finance intern (Feb 2015 – Feb 2016) Enerfín Sociedad de energía (Elecnor Group)

Co-Founder and administrator (Jun 2018 – Feb 2021) Mundo Orenda NGO (www.mundoorenda.org)

Education

Dual Bachelor Degree: Business Administration & Laws Universidad de Córdoba | Spain

Masters's Degree in Economical and Financial Management CEF Estudios Financieros | Madrid, Spain

Computer Science 42 Programming school | Málaga, Spain